http://www.hitchplug.com/privacy.php

Hitch Plugs for your Trailer and Tow Hitch Receivers - Hitch Plug .com
| Log In | Shipping | Contact Us
HomeAuto Brand Hitch PlugsSports Hitch PlugsLighted Hitch PlugsAll-American Hitch Plugs
Auto Brand Hitch Plugs  Ford Hitch Plugs  Chevy Hitch Plugs  GMC Hitch Plugs  Dodge Hitch Plugs  Cadillac Hitch Plugs  Lincoln Hitch Plugs  Jeep Hitch Plugs  Hummer Hitch Plugs  Nissan Hitch PlugsSports Hitch Plugs  College Hitch Plugs  NFL Hitch Plugs  MLB Hitch Plugs  NASCAR Hitch PlugsLighted Hitch Plugs  Lighted Hitch Brakes  Lighted Hitch PlugsAll-American Hitch Plugs  Military Hitch Plugs  Patriotic Hitch Plugs  Fire & Rescue Hitch PlugsNovelty Hitch Plugs  Flag Hitch Plugs  Animal Hitch Plugs  Religious Hitch Plugs  Propeller Hitch Plugs  Hitch Steps  Unique Hitch PlugsHobby Hitch Plugs  Motorcycling Hitch Plugs  Hunting Hitch Plugs  Fishing Hitch Plugs  Golf Hitch Plugs
Hitch Plug .com : Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only.Collection of InformationThis site collects personally identifiable information, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., that are voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your order. If you choose to opt in to our email notifications then your information may also be used to send you emails regarding sales and specials. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.TrackingThis site tracks useful information such as browser type and operating system, the number of visitors to the site, and how visitors use the site. Personal information cannot be collected through our tracking. IP Addresses An IP address is a number which is used to identify computers so that data such as Web pages you request can be sent to you. Our Web server automatically collects IP addresses for purposes of administering our system and to help us diagnose problems with our server. Distribution of InformationWe will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. Commitment to Data SecurityYour personally identifiable information is kept secure. Customers who buy through this website are shopping on a secure server, which encrypts all of the customer’s personal information including name, address and credit card number. Encryption ensures only authorized employees have access to this information.Consent By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us according to this privacy policy.Users Under the Age of 13 If you are under the age of 13, do not provide any personally identifiable information on this site without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Call: 1-888-537-0703  QtyItemPriceYou've Got Nothingin Your Cart! Sub Total:$0.00 Shipping:$?.?? Grand Total:$0.00Shipping To: ALAKAZARCACOCTDEDCFLGAHIIDILINIAKSKYLAMEMDMAMIMNMSMOMTNENVNHNJNMNYNCNDOHOKORPARISCSDTNTXUTVTVAWAWVWIWY
Privacy PolicyThis site was designed byDigital Hill Multimedia Inc.www.hitchplug.com
